// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "--------- is the father of computer.",
    answer: "Charles Babbage",
    options: [
      "Herman Hollerith",
      "Ada Byron",
      "Blaise Pascal",
      "Charles Babbage"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Tabulating Machine was invented by -------",
    answer: "Herman Hollerith",
    options: [
      "Blaise Pascal",
      "Herman Hollerith",
      "Ada Byron",
      "Charles Babbage"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A desktop computer is also known as",
    answer: "PC",
    options: [
      "PC",
      "Laptop",
      "Mainframe",
      "Palmtop"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "CPU is the --------- of computer.",
    answer: "Brain",
    options: [
      "Brain",
      "Ear",
      "Eye",
      "All above these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "----------- computer is the most powerful computer.",
    answer: "Super",
    options: [
      "Mini",
      "Micro",
      "Super",
      "Mainframe"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "----------- is the physical device of a computer system.",
    answer: "Hardware",
    options: [
      "Program",
      "Software",
      "Hardware",
      "Application"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "IC stands for",
    answer: "Integrated Circuit",
    options: [
      "Internal Circuit",
      "Internal Computer",
      "Integrated Computer",
      "Integrated Circuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is not a characteristic of a computer?",
    answer: "Intelligence",
    options: [
      "Speed",
      "Intelligence",
      "Automation",
      "Versatility"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not Computer Hardware?",
    answer: "Antivirus",
    options: [
      "Mouse",
      "Monitor",
      "Printer",
      "Antivirus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "----------- processing is used in mainframe computer.",
    answer: "Batch",
    options: [
      "Parallel",
      "Batch",
      "Toggle",
      "Serial"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Computer is a/an ----------",
    answer: "electronic device",
    options: [
      "battery",
      "input device",
      "monitoring device",
      "electronic device"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Abacus was developed by",
    answer: "China",
    options: [
      "China",
      "India",
      "America",
      "Germany"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The first computer was programmed using",
    answer: "Machine language",
    options: [
      "Assembly language",
      "Machine language",
      "Source code",
      "Object code"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The main characteristic of fourth generation was",
    answer: "VLSI",
    options: [
      "Transistor",
      "Vacuum tubes",
      "Integrated circuit",
      "VLSI"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "----------- is used in first generation computer.",
    answer: "Vacuum tubes",
    options: [
      "Transistors",
      "Vacuum tubes",
      "Microprocessor",
      "Integrated circuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "----------- is used in third generation computer.",
    answer: "Integrated circuit",
    options: [
      "Transistors",
      "Vacuum tubes",
      "Microprocessor",
      "Integrated circuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "----------- is used in second generation computer.",
    answer: "Transistors",
    options: [
      "Transistors",
      "Vacuum tubes",
      "Microprocessor",
      "Integrated circuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The CPU and Primary memory are located on the.",
    answer: "motherboard",
    options: [
      "expansion board",
      "storage device",
      "motherboard",
      "output device"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Numeric pad is in the -----------",
    answer: "keyboard",
    options: [
      "speaker",
      "keyboard",
      "mouse",
      "monitor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "FORTRAN is useful in ----------- sector.",
    answer: "scientific purpose",
    options: [
      "Office management",
      "census analysis",
      "business purpose",
      "scientific purpose"
    ]
  },
];